Hello everyone! This is Newly Realeased Cool Joy!
This time, it's our first dance class!
Good morning! Nice to meet you.
I'm supposed to have one corporate tie-up today.
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry to tell you this, but it's not true.
Wow!
It's a lie.
So here is today's project.
Please read on.
Ozawa Imi's First Surprise Challenge
I successfully recorded a fake ad deal while the members were accusing me of lying.
I did it!
I've been wanting to set this up.
She's grinning.
Ads.
Let's lower the ads.
Here you go!
This time it's a surprise challenge with me, Ozawa Imi, as the trickster!
Besides, Mika is also calling the members to take care of you in terms of getting ad time!
But that smorgasbord is a super sour and very bad drink!
We have three missions for the members who might be suspicious.
Mission number one, get one of them to drink it again.
2. Make everyone drink to make a toast together.
3. Make one member drink it, saying that someone has to drink it all.
This is the first time for me to surprise everyone, so I feel really bad about it.
But now that I'm in charge, I'm going to give it my all.
I'll do my best.
Good morning.
What's up?
Right?
I really like these two.
There are so many of them here today,
I've got a lot of people here today, but I've finally got a visitor from the medical staff, and I guess this is the first time for you, Shimeji-san.
Thank you very much.
This will be an exploration video.
I haven't worn a jacket in a while,
This time, we are going to explore like it's March.
So, I'm a little more firm than usual,
I hope you will all show your best side,
I'd like you all to show me your best side,
I'd like you all to show us your good points, but this is a product introduction,
We would like you to do a better job than usual.
And since the sponsor and the waiter are here, I would like to thank you all for your cooperation,
Thank you very much.
This is a company that offers smoothies in Tokyo,
This will be the work company that is on D.SAN.
D&E, a little bit of diagonal hassle, please.
I am the production person,
I'm a production person, but I receive such items,
Sales person,
Katsunori Takemoto, please take care of them.
Please take care of them.
He is doing a great job.
I have some materials on smoothies that I would like to introduce to you this time,
I would like to ask you to explain it first.
Mr. Takemoto, please.
D&E Corporation,
Five smoothies,
This is a gift.
That's an outline of the product. This is a new smoothie for working women in the city,
It is a blend of many fruits, and was developed to be an energizing smoothie with a strong acidity.
Next page. The concept is that even when you don't have energy, even when you don't feel like it, you can still do it,
You can still do it, you can still do it, you can still do it, you can still do it, and you can still do it.
We have a blend of 18 different kinds of smoothies based on trocchai, lekomis and bananas, and we are aiming for the survival of the smoothie.
It's a taste of the city. It is a blend of 18 kinds.
Please don't give a negative impression, such as too sour or too hard to drink.
Please do not give a negative impression, such as too acidic or hard to drink.
Thank you very much.
Is that how it is? Do you have any questions?
No, I'm fine.
Then, let's just write down the signals, shall we?
Yes, sir.
I'm not sure if you have a script or not, but I'd like to give you a pure taste of what we're going to do.
Where is the store?
There are many working women and fashionable stores in Taiwan and Japan, but we don't do recommendations.
Yes, thank you very much.Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Shall I set you up?
Yes, ma'am.
How's Mai-chan?
Yes, sir.
And the tournament.
Aren't you excited?
Let's go for it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm changing from a little bit of a person right now
Yes, even now
Shall I give them all a straw?
Thank you very much.
I feel like I'm getting there.
It's coming together.
Mix it up.
Oh, yes, thank you very much.
Looks easy to drink.
Thank you very much.
Nice straw.
It's kind of sweet
I drank it all in the beginning.
I don't know.
It smells so good.
Oh, my God, it's so cool.
You can tell, can't you?
Here are the products I'd like to introduce to you!
Wow!
This product is not yet on the market.
but we are able to try it out
but we were able to try it out first.
Let's drink it together right away!
Thank you very much!
I don't know, I'm still waiting for the pre-launch.
This is the best!
I'm so happy!
Well, may I go first?
Yes, I'll have some.
It smells so good.
It's so fruity.
Fruity?
Bon appétit.
What do you think? It's good.
I want some! I want some!
It's kind of sour.
It's sour, but it's really good for you.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good.
It's not spicy, right?
LOL.
I'm picking this up right now.
I'm picking it up.
Yummy.
Well, how about you, Mr. Poner?
I'm not much of a smoothie drinker.
But you know what? I can drink a smoothie.
It's sour and easy to drink.
Oh, wow.
It's got a sour taste.
I can feel the heavy chopsticks.
I can feel the chopsticks.
Just a sip.
This, this, and this...
Chubashi.
Here you go, Riko.
How is it?
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Delicious!
Ha-ha-ha!
You know...
I love acidity.
Yeah, all the time.
I wonder what's in this.
I wonder what's in it.What's in it.
It's citrusy.
But it's really easy to drink.
Can I drink it all?
You can drink it.
Just feel it.
You'll love it, Biko.
It's so good!
It's really easy to drink.
Does it have a hint of plum?
Really?
Why?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'd like to taste it.
Yes, please.
May I?
Yes, just go ahead and guzzle it already.
Bon appétit.
Dainty.
Oh, wow.
What?
It's totally different from what I thought the head would taste like.
I don't know how to say it.
The aroma was quite sweet.
But the plums, the plums inside...
What?
It's very sour at first.
But after that, it's very sweet.
And then there's some kind of tangerine.
The sweetness stays.
It's so refreshing and easy to drink.
Is it good?
Yes, it's delicious.
Let's all make a toast.
Cheers!
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Delicious.
It sure smells good.
Plum?
Plum? I don't know.
It's plum-y.
Elingo.
Wait a minute, please.
Wait a minute.
It's really delicious.
Go ahead.
It's so good!
It's so good, I can feel it in my mouth!
It's definitely got a plum flavor, right?
It's delicious!
Are you okay? You've had too much to drink.
It's in someone's head.
So fast!
That's great.
From where?
It's delicious.
It's great.
It's safe.
Quick!
Taste it, taste it, taste it.
I'm tasting it.
Quick!
I've been chugging away here, chugging away.
I'm tired, okay?
Are you okay? - I'm fine. I'm just trying to stay energized.
That was fast! That's what I'm talking about.
This is really good.
I love it.
So...
Lucky!
What do you mean?
What?
It's not true.
The smoothie's a lie.
What's this?
I thought it was a little sour.I thought it was a little sour.
Riko gobbled it up so fast.
It was a little tasty.
I can't stop salivating.
You're doing great.
I'm so embarrassed.
You look a little sour.
Is there any plum in it?
No plums.
I drank a lot.
Not too much?
Riko was going to drink it.
As part of our mission.
Make someone a member.
Riko kept saying that to me.
So I said it.
It's great!
I drank it.
My lips are sour.
Wait a minute.
Conor, you shouldn't have.
It's Conner. It's so sour.
Everyone's pacing is a little crazy.
It's a little crazy.
But I'm trying to get people to trust me.
I thought I'd have to do a few.
It's a little sour.
I'm pretty good.
I've been turning red lately.
I've been turning red.
I thought it was about time.
It's not a smoothie.
The D&U one?
My Chaini.
D&U.
It's a surprise. It's a lie.
There were clues scattered all over the place.
There were hints scattered all over the place.
The materials?
You mean like this?
Like this?
It's not a tie-up at all.
And everyone was in suits.
I was so nervous.
Everyone's in jackets.
I'm so energetic!
Yay!
It's so mashed up.
Oh, wow.
If you read it vertically.
Eww...
It's very mazy.
It's very tasteless.
I didn't know the aroma could be so good.
I liked it the first time.
The lko is very strong.
But thank you... for drinking it.
It's sour here.
It's the lychee that makes it sour.
This is Parisian Apple.
That's great. - Ace.
We're aces.
Where did you get the word "kojingmaru" from?
Well... kojimmal is...
It's Korean.
It's a lie.
It means "lie.
Woooo...
Kojimmal.
You have to be aware of kojimmal.
Smoothie.
You call it a smoothie.
That's where it goes wrong.
So, this was my first surprise project.
I'm going to surprise you for the first time in my life.
Me too.
Rico...
I thought it wasn't a surprise.
That's why I'm drinking it.
I have to.I have to drink.
I didn't drink.
It smells like conoisseur.
I knew it was sour.
Conoa stops the sperm from coming in here.
That's why I didn't drink it.
It's too good.
So, I'm a little weird about this.
It's sour.
The drink is unusually short on the scale.
That's right.
Let's have a nice, quiet toast.
Let's all have a toast.
Let's have another drink.
So, if you liked this video, please leave a
If you liked this video, please leave a comment with a high rating
and subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now.
This is Nyarikonjay.
Bye bye!
Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing Before Doing
I thought it was some kind of unannounced baggage check, so I thought I'd clean up a little bit.
That's why we're making it that way.